Mind out.
Move!
Look, on the west wall!
Get down to the crypt!
Just hold.
We'll take him.
- Come on, help the lads! - Yes, my lady.
Quickly, now! Quickly! Get those in position.
- Come on. - Close the gate!
That's it.
Oh, for fuck's sake. You took your time.
Do you speak their tongue?
Tell them to lift their swords.
Valar morghulis.
Valar dohaeris.
Open the gate!
Come. Come on.
Easy.
There's no need to execute me, Ser Davos.
I'll be dead before the dawn.
The Night King is coming.
The dead are already here.
Stand your ground!
Get down to the crypt.
I'm not abandoning my people.
Take this and go.
I don't know how to use it.
Stick them with the pointy end.
Edd!
Sam, get up!
Oh, God. Sam.
Edd!
Fall back! Fall back!
Fall back!
Come on!
Open the gate!
Let us in!
Keep moving!
Come on!
- Keep moving, fast. - To your posts.
- Go! - Keep moving!
Come on, run!
Keep moving!
Dany!
Grab your weapon now!
Guard the barricades!
Through that pass!
Close up the gaps!
Go! Hey! Go! Go!
Get in! Get in!
Get in! Come on!
Move!
- Come on!  - Come on!
-Come on!   - Come on!
Protect the gate!
They're coming! Come on!
Fall back!
Light the trench!
- Wait!  - Light the trench!
She can't see us.
Light the trenches!
With a torch, light the trenches!
- Right there.  - Torch it!
Light the trenches!
Clegane.
You must try not to worry yourself.
分析，谁会活到最后？
上知乎搜索「权游谁会死」，给出你的神预测
At least we're already in a crypt.
If we were up there,
we might see something everyone else is missing.
Something that makes a difference.
What?
Remember the Battle of Blackwater?
I brought us through the Mud Gate.
And got your face cut in half.
And it made a difference.
If I was out there right now...
You'd die.
There's nothing you can do.
You might be surprised at the lengths I'd go
to avoid joining the Army of the Dead.
I could think of no organization less suited to my talents.
Witty remarks won't make a difference.
That's why we're down here, none of us can do anything.
It's the truth.
It's the most heroic thing we can do now...
look the truth in the face.
Maybe we should have stayed married.
You were the best of them.
What a terrifying thought.
It wouldn't work between us.
Why not?
The Dragon Queen.
Your divided loyalties would become a problem.
Yes.
Without the Dragon Queen, there'd be no problem at all.
We'd all be dead already.
They lit the trench.
Bran...
I just want you to know...
I wish--
The things I did--
Everything you did brought you where you are now.
Where you belong.
Home.
I'm going to go now.
Go where?
Man the walls!
Man the wall!
Come on!
Get out there! Get moving!
Come on. Come on! Come on!
Go, go, go!
Come on!
They're against the wall!
Get more men up here!
- Fill the gaps, quickly! - Get in there!
They're climbing the walls!
- Relieve the archers! - Relieve the archers!
Archers on top!
- Move up! - Go, go! Come here!
- Come on! - Move back!
- Stand away! - Go on, go on. Go! Go.
- Step back. - All the way, archers!
Hold the wall!
The wall, they're coming up!
- Hold the wall! - Hold the wall!
Draw!
Come on!
They're coming up!
Look out!
Clegane!
Clegane, we need you!
You can't give up on us.
Fuck off! We can't beat them.
Don't you see that, you stupid whore?
We're fighting Death!
They can't beat Death.
Tell her that.
Open the door!
- Come on! - Open the door!
Please!
Open it!
Come on! Go!
- Come on! - Run!
We've gotta go!
The Lord brought him back for a purpose.
Now that purpose has been served.
I know you.
And I know you.
You said we'd meet again.
And here we are.
At the end of the world.
You said I'd shut many eyes forever.
You were right about that too.
Brown eyes...
green eyes...
and blue eyes.
What do we say to the God of Death?
Not today.
Here they come!
Steady, lads.
Steady now.
Make every shot count.
Over there!
There!
Get off.
Dracarys.
Come on! Come on!
No! No, no, no!
- Bran! - Go!
Jorah!
Theon.
You're a good man.
Thank you.
I'm hurt.